Hello to all the brothers.  Brother, what I am
saying today is that the yellow number
plate is for a car, Temo ji, it is a truck,
brother.  Yes, the taxi numbers and cars are
my friend, my brother, the younger one is
with him, the big forward has happened.  He
bought a new car 5 months ago and two-three
months ago that car met with an accident.   An
accident happens.  So let me
show you the photo of the accident.
How much damage do you think is happening
inside this car?  Brother, show me this car
carefully.  Have you seen the car?
How much damage do you think this car has
?  How much damage do
you think this car would have suffered?  He made a bill of ₹2,71,000 for this car.  Let me
show you what I have.  The
final bill of this vehicle is of ₹271000
brother, I have got this work done from DD Motor,
you can see this from Maruti,
I will also share this bill of DD Motor with you in the
video, it was done with zero dep
insurance brother, the company does it,
even after that ₹45000 have been taken from them.
This is the receipt for which he made this payment yesterday.
Brother, show me the receipt carefully.
So brother, we want to tell everyone that you should
not get insurance from ICICI.  This is the dirtiest and
worst company.  Firstly, his brothers'
car was parked for three months.
He paid the EMI by borrowing money from here and there.
After that, ₹45,000 were taken from them.  Why did you
take ₹45,000 brother?  Only and only through
hooliganism.  He said that you will have to make 10%
payment.  Their survey says that
your car will be repaired only if you
make 10% payment.  The boy had less knowledge,
why would we do it 10%?  When we have the
license everything is ok complete.  No,
your car will again be a total loss
because we did not know that our car would be lost.
He said, okay, I will give it to you.  Why will you give it
brother?  I talked to him and you became me.
Brother, why should we give 10%?  So he was saying that he will have to give it.
Brother, despite having zero dep insurance,
they took 10% payment from the customer.   The
bill for the car was ₹71,000.  After that
took 10% payment.  Even after that the tyres of the car were
not changed.  When the car behind was towed, the
rear tyres were worn out.   Did
not change the tyres.  I said, please
check the minimum kilometer.  The car covered 5000 km.   She has gone.  The
tyre said, brother, I will not give you the tyre.  There is no
insurance company worse than this.
We had got some work done at Maruti in Narla
and I had also
posted a video against it earlier.  Brother, he is such a
mean man, stay away from him.  Now you
can see that in that car, you might be feeling that
this payment of ₹2,71,000 has been made
by the insurance company for this car yesterday.   In
which the customer has made the payment of ₹45,000
from his own pocket.  Payment of ₹45,000.
So brother, instead of getting trapped in the greed of ₹200-400, get the
insurance done from your brother, any relative or any acquaintance and
not from any low-level person
and the most interesting thing is that
this insurance was done by Maruti company itself.
He took the car from Badli.  He got
his insurance done.  When they insured it, they did
not insure the plastic, etc., the markings, etc., the nuts and bolts.  Hey brother
you could have taken ₹500 more from the customer you would have covered it at
least now the customer should pay
₹5000 as 3 months installment hey brother if
he has so much money then why would he buy a taxi number
car he will do his own business
someone will do his own work so brother
beware of these thugs these people also do not tell the customer
brother what is there in it and what is not there when he is
taking the next loan and depositing ₹1500 for the car then will
he not pay ₹500 he will
pay ₹500 but why does the insurance company
trap them if they do not have any sense then they will
take money from the customer also now for ₹71000
in the car I think there will be a loss of even one lakh the
way the car was now after opening
this car brother it was surveyed thrice brother it was done today then after 10
days then again after 15 days
why should they survey once brother there is
so much loss so after surveying thrice then they
take ₹45000 from the customer
Brother, don't take any insurance from today.  If you have any kind
of problem or trouble, or need any help,
I am ready to provide it, brother.
Yes, but brother, stay away from these thugs.
Hello to all brothers.  I will
keep posting photos to you.  You can see all the photos.